row	col	id	content	tokens	lemmaTokens	posTags	nerTags	nerValues	number	date	num2	list
-1	0	fb:row.row.frequency	Frequency	frequency	frequency	NN	O					
-1	1	fb:row.row.call_sign	Call sign	call|sign	call|sign	VB|NN	O|O	|				
-1	2	fb:row.row.name	Name	name	name	NN	O					
-1	3	fb:row.row.format	Format	format	format	NN	O					
-1	4	fb:row.row.owner	Owner	owner	owner	NN	O					
-1	5	fb:row.row.target_city_market	Target city/market	target|city/market	target|city/market	NN|NN	O|O	|				
-1	6	fb:row.row.city_of_license	City of license	city|of|license	city|of|license	NN|IN|NN	O|O|O	||				
0	0	fb:cell.89_7_fm	89.7 FM	89.7|fm	89.7|FM	CD|NNP	NUMBER|O	89.7|	89.7			
0	1	fb:cell.kusd	KUSD	kusd	KUSD	NNP	PERSON					
0	2	fb:cell.south_dakota_public_broadcasting	South Dakota Public Broadcasting	south|dakota|public|broadcasting	South|Dakota|Public|Broadcasting	NNP|NNP|NNP|NNP	LOCATION|LOCATION|O|O	|||				
0	3	fb:cell.npr	NPR	npr	NPR	NNP	ORGANIZATION					
0	4	fb:cell.sd_board_of_directors_for_educational_telecommunications	SD Board of Directors for Educational Telecommunications	sd|board|of|directors|for|educational|telecommunications	sd|board|of|director|for|educational|telecommunications	NN|NN|IN|NNS|IN|JJ|NNS	O|O|O|O|O|O|O	||||||				SD Board of Directors for Educational Telecommunications
0	5	fb:cell.yankton_vermillion	Yankton/Vermillion	yankton/vermillion	yankton/vermillion	NN	O					Yankton|Vermillion
0	6	fb:cell.vermillion	Vermillion	vermillion	Vermillion	NNP	O					
1	0	fb:cell.93_1_fm	93.1 FM	93.1|fm	93.1|FM	CD|NNP	NUMBER|O	93.1|	93.1			
1	1	fb:cell.kkya	KKYA	kkya	KKYA	NNP	PERSON					
1	2	fb:cell.kk93	KK93	kk93	kk93	NN	O		93.0			
1	3	fb:cell.country	Country	country	country	NN	O					
1	4	fb:cell.riverfront_broadcasting_llc	Riverfront Broadcasting LLC	riverfront|broadcasting|llc	riverfront|broadcasting|llc	NN|NN|NN	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||				Riverfront Broadcasting LLC
1	5	fb:cell.yankton_vermillion	Yankton/Vermillion	yankton/vermillion	yankton/vermillion	NN	O					Yankton|Vermillion
1	6	fb:cell.yankton	Yankton	yankton	Yankton	NNP	LOCATION					
2	0	fb:cell.94_3_fm	94.3 FM	94.3|fm	94.3|FM	CD|NNP	NUMBER|O	94.3|	94.3			
2	1	fb:cell.kdam	KDAM	kdam	KDAM	NNP	PERSON					
2	2	fb:cell.the_dam	The Dam	the|dam	the|dam	DT|NN	O|O	|				
2	3	fb:cell.mainstream_rock	Mainstream Rock	mainstream|rock	Mainstream|Rock	NNP|NNP	O|O	|				
2	4	fb:cell.riverfront_broadcasting_llc	Riverfront Broadcasting LLC	riverfront|broadcasting|llc	riverfront|broadcasting|llc	NN|NN|NN	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION	||				Riverfront Broadcasting LLC
2	5	fb:cell.yankton_vermillion	Yankton/Vermillion	yankton/vermillion	yankton/vermillion	NN	O					Yankton|Vermillion
2	6	fb:cell.hartington	Hartington	hartington	Hartington	NNP	PERSON					
3	0	fb:cell.104_1_fm	104.1 FM	104.1|fm	104.1|FM	CD|NNP	NUMBER|O	104.1|	104.1			
3	1	fb:cell.wnax_fm	WNAX-FM	wnax|fm	WNAX|FM	NNP|NNP	O|O	|				
3	2	fb:cell.the_wolf_104_1	The Wolf 104.1	the|wolf|104.1	the|Wolf|104.1	DT|NNP|CD	O|O|NUMBER	||104.1	104.1			
3	3	fb:cell.country	Country	country	country	NN	O					
3	4	fb:cell.saga_communications	Saga Communications	saga|communications	saga|communication	NN|NNS	O|O	|				Saga Communications
3	5	fb:cell.yankton_vermillion	Yankton/Vermillion	yankton/vermillion	yankton/vermillion	NN	O					Yankton|Vermillion
3	6	fb:cell.yankton	Yankton	yankton	Yankton	NNP	LOCATION					
4	0	fb:cell.106_3_fm	106.3 FM	106.3|fm	106.3|FM	CD|NNP	NUMBER|O	106.3|	106.3			
4	1	fb:cell.kvht	KVHT	kvht	KVHT	NNP	PERSON					
4	2	fb:cell.classic_hits_106_3	Classic Hits 106.3	classic|hits|106.3	classic|hit|106.3	JJ|NNS|CD	O|O|NUMBER	||106.3	106.3			
4	3	fb:cell.classic_hits	Classic Hits	classic|hits	classic|hit	JJ|NNS	O|O	|				
4	4	fb:cell.cullhane_communications_inc	Cullhane Communications, Inc.	cullhane|communications|,|inc.|.	Cullhane|Communications|,|Inc.|.	NNP|NNPS|,|NNP|.	ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|ORGANIZATION|O	||||				Cullhane Communications|Inc.
4	5	fb:cell.yankton_vermillion	Yankton/Vermillion	yankton/vermillion	yankton/vermillion	NN	O					Yankton|Vermillion
4	6	fb:cell.vermillion	Vermillion	vermillion	Vermillion	NNP	O					
